[{"answer": "He's Lance Hunt!  Just take off the glasse", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "A vague similarity?  IT'S THE SAME GUY", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Leave him alone.  She's his mother, not yours", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "So when are we gonna have an on night", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " What does it matter?  Women just want to control yo", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Who's chicken?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I knew you'd cone.  I left that skylight open for you", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I knew you'd know", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I know you did", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I know you knew I'd know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I knew you'd know", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "But did you know I knew you'd know I'd know", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "This looks like a job for Superma", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Or both", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Everything's going exactly as we planned", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It must have slipped my mind", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I got this cousin.  He's a real doofus, but he claims he can become invisible", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "How could I see him if he's invisible", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "He was the last time I saw him", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I was eight", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, I give to the that place, and I feel that sort of cover", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " My weapons? You need my weapons", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It is", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " You're nuts", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And the nuts always call themselves great", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I use it... to fight evil", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " It is", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " my friend... this is wonderful", "docId": "Mystery-Men.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I always knew that you were special", "qsentId": 30}]